http://www.apositivechange.com/faq/apositiva-privacy-statement/

Privacy Policy | Apositiva | Portland Oregon Hypnotherapy and Coaching
Information Collection and Use
This is our updated privacy policy for Apositiva clients, students, and users who opt-in to receive specific communications. Apositiva is the sole owner of the information and content collected on this site. We collect, use and process User data according to this Privacy Policy. Apositiva will not sell, rent, or share this information with others in ways different from what is disclosed in our agreement and this statement. The Apositiva.com site collects information with opt-in permission from our students and clients at several different points on our Web site. Client information is stored for reasons required by U.S. law for the required period of time and then shredded. This information is considered private and will only be used for purposes as agreed upon.
Registration
In order to receive e-mails from Apositiva, newsletters, or receive special promotions, use certain sections or services of this website, a user must first complete our Registration form and opt-in. During Registration a user is requested to give specific contact information, which may include user first name, last name and email address. This information is used to contact the user and provide information about the services on our site that our users have expressed interest.
Cookies
No cookies are placed on user sites from Apositiva.com. Permission is not given to our business partners to use cookies on our site (i.e. advertisers, affiliates).
Log Files
As the web gathers information, we may utilize IP addresses to review usage, analyze trends, administer our site, track user’s movement, and potentially gather demographic information for aggregate use. Please note that IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Sharing
We may share aggregated demographic information with our professional partners.
Billing and Shipping
Apositiva accepts payment via money order, check, credit cards (i.e. Visa and MasterCard), PayPal and Google Checkout. We may use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies are not permitted to retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Apositiva will partner with affiliates and other businesses to provide specific products and services. When Apositiva users sign up for these services, we may share information necessary for the third party to provide these services, such as name, e-mail and shipping address. These affiliates and business partners are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Links
The Apositiva.com web site contains links to other sites. Apositiva is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. It is advisable for users to be aware that when they leave the Apositiva site that they should read the privacy statements of each web site they enter, and understand how that website collects and manages personally identifiable information. The privacy statement for Apositiva applies solely to information collected by Apositiva.
Newsletters
Apositiva provides news and special offers. If a user desires to subscribe to our newsletter, we request contact information such as an first name, last name, and email address. Mailing lists from our newsletter providers such as MailChimp provide double opt-ins so that Users may choose and confirm their desired settings.
Online Classes
Apositiva partners with online learning platforms that require clear consent. For example, In cases where Users sign up for a class on Ruzuku.com, where Apositiva offers self-paced classes, the User will only receive updates and information on the selected class, unless they sign up for other classes on that platform. We are  happy to help any student who wants to exercise the right to be forgotten by removing the User account from the course and our database. Users may receive information
Special Offers
Apositiva respects our users. New users signing up for newsletters will receive a verification request, so they can confirm their request. Regular clients and students may occasionally receive announcements or information about our products and services. Users may opt out of this program at any time.
Choice/Opt-out
Apositiva users may opt out for receiving newsletters or e-mails. It is not our intention to spam our users.
Unsubscribing is simple. Apositiva users who are no longer interested in receiving mails or newsletters may opt out of receiving these communications by referencing “unsubscribe” in the subject line in the email and return to cat.wilson@apositiva.com.
Notification of Changes
We maintain the right to make changes to this policy at our discretion or as certain laws require.
Contact
If you are aware of any misinformation or have any concerns, please contact us immediately via e-mail to cat.wilson@apositiva.com.
Share...Google+FacebookTwitterLinkedinemailPinterest
Recent Posts
Negative Stuff Bugging You?
Head Bump!
Negative Stuff Bugging You?
Head Bump!
